Hello everyone, my name is Tamaki Ishizuka, and today I'm here at Tokyo Dome, a place I've longed to visit.
Today's game is against the Yokohama DNA Bay Stars, so I'd like to watch the game with this gentleman.
Okay.
Hello, I'm Haruo Yamaguchi.
I think today's an important game for both sides, but last week, when we had the Hyuga Festival, we won one game and lost one game, so...
Yes, I hope we can win today.
I really want to win today. If the Giants win today, the magic lights up.
I will do my best to win.
I'm not going to stop early, but I'm going to cheer for them.
Have you ever been to a baseball game at the Tokyo Dome? I've never been to a baseball game, but I've stood up once.
But you've been to one, right? Yes, so have I. But it's already been decided, so let's watch it with that in mind.
We're going to stand here in three months. I can see the visitor's park now.
Do you have a favorite player or someone you support?
Miyazaki.
That's right.
I'm thinking about buying a new Japan.
You should buy it.
This is for sure if you work out at Okama Stadium
Miyazaki's Visitor's Uniform.
Huh?
Huh? It's not here.
Visitor's uniform.
What? Huh?
Is it there?
Yes.
Is it gone?
No.
We can change it, right?
I'll give it to Watara.
So does Watarashi.
Watarashi is also available in size S.
I'll go with S.
I bought a digital winiform.
I'm happy because I didn't have it
I'm glad.
Okay, next we'll get some Giants merchandise.
Okay.
I'll take it.
Really? Oh, my God.
I'm so excited!
I'm so happy for you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Where are you, over there?
This way, this way, this way, this way.
Here's my shopping.
Spring is so awkward... I'm surrounded... spring is so awkward...
Then stick with me. First of all... I'm a sucker for random stuff.
There's a lot of stuff here.
I'll take this one and this one.
I'm looking for an Enlightenment. This one here, this one here...
This one? Yes, yes. You have an Enlightenment? I use them between the shells.
Which one should we choose?
But... Shoko Asano. She's the same age as me.
She's playing in the army right now. She's amazing.
I'll have a towel that says, “This is the best!
I'd like to make a towel called “Unipatchin” with her, but I'd like to make a towel called “Unipatchin” with the slogan “2024”.
No, wait!
We'll use the 90th anniversary logo.
We'll put the original number and name on it.
Shall we make it 46?
I'm going with 46. I'm going with 46.
Forty-six.
Wow!
That's amazing.
That's a standard.
I'm excited.
I'm so excited.
That's great.
Printland after this
Oh, here comes the paper!
Ta-da!
I'll assemble it with this
It's 46 stone mounds.
Then put it in here and patch it up,
It's going to be a uniform.
Is this enough for the bijoux?
For the bijouter.
Yay, yay!
That's 46.
What should we do? A name.
Haruyo, I guess.
Haruyo.
It sounds strong.
Why?
She seems strong.
Standard.
It's done.
Did you do it?
Yes, it's done.
This one is done.
Let's do it later.
I will make it later.
I just finished buying the goods, so I'll go inside.
Please. Please show us the way.
I'll take care of it.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
Ta-da.
I'll make it now.
Please open it first.
Yes, sir.
Like this.
Put the two sides together.
That's right.
Ta-da!
Oh, my God.
I'm glad they match.
That's nice.
I'm glad we match.
Matching.
Cheers.
We've been soundly defeated. - We've been soundly defeated. - We've been soundly defeated.
We've been unilaterally defeated.
Yes, sir.
Yokohama Leader Base.
Number 1, Kajiwara Naito.
Kajiwara Naito on first.
Kajiwara Naito at second.
No. 4, Osumi.
Osumi
No.5, Osumi.
Osumi, amazing!
Osumi is scary!
He hits so hard!
No.5, Miyazaki
The other day
Miyazaki
Miyazaki player
So you're No. 5?
Number 5, number 5
Number 5, number 5.
Number 9, pitcher, Jackson.
Ya-ya!
Mr. Tsukasaka was the pitcher when he threw out the first pitch.
Starting pitcher.
No.1, Yoshino.
Number 1, Yoshino.
He's an unshakeable No. 1.
He's steadfast?
Yes, sir.
Number 5, Yoshino.
Oh.
I'm downstairs.
Oh, oh,
We're doing a live show here.
And for Christmas.
When? It's already September.
In three months.
Three months? That's fast.
I've never been to Tokyo Dome for a concert.
I've never been to Tokyo Dome for a live concert.
I don't even know what the view is like.
I don't even know what the view is like, but it's really big.
The stage is right there.
Right there.
There are seats right here on the field.
I was allowed to stand there once.
But I couldn't speak at that time.
I couldn't speak at the time, so when the call goes up...
It's going to be amazing.
I'll be so moved.
This is Hamaguchi.
Hamaguchi?
He's looking for a lot of investment.
That's it?
Here we go.
He's got a “C” ten.
That's great.
Next is a uniform key chain!
This is Kadowaki!
Number 5.
Kadowaki!
Here we go!
No, it's not.
It's Nagano.
Wait, wait!
He's the one who bought the penlight!
That's right.
You mean you're classmates or the same age?
But we're not classmates.
but
Asano joined in 2022 too.
I joined in 2022 too.
Same classmate?
What? What year did you join?
I joined Hyugaizaka in 2020.
He joined Hinatazaka.
That's not good.
The judges are pink.
So cute!
I like pink too, so I'm happy.
One minute later
Batter number one.
If I can beat the first batter
Batter No. 1
The 1st batter
Batter No.1
Kajiwara
The top of the 1st inning
Batting first is nerve-wracking, isn't it?
Kajiwara
If we can get the first batter out of the inning
the flow of the game goes away...
The flow of the game...
But if I hit here, the tide will turn our way.
This at-bat is important.
It's important.
He launched it.
Sakamoto got it.
An infield single.
He went for the start.
Sano!
Sano.
He's going to hit it.
Number 7.
He's got two outs.
He's out. He's out.
We've got him cornered.
He's going down for the second out.
That's right.
Backward.
Toward the back.
Is the ball hit hard?
It's a hard ball.
You hit the bullseye.
What's the problem?
Well, well, well.
It's only the first inning.
Let's eat in between.
In between.
Oh, here they come.
First one.
I'm trying to keep up.
But I'm just now
Finished
I like to watch TV.
I like Crash.
The center of all is MARUI
The best center is Marui
Let's eat
Let's eat!
The center is Marui
I'm scared of MARUI
I'm scared of Marui!
Yay!
Oh!
Well then, Pressure, let's wait for this one!
Kobayashi of Pressure was the real deal for the next season, '14.
Even though Kobayashi and Shin contribute quite a bit,
The novice player, Nitta,
In the third round,
Already,
Only 100 points.
Hooray!
Hooray! Hooray!
Oh, it's Maru-sensei's turn.
Oh, no.
Oh no.
Nahomira, I've been shot.
Maru!
Lukan.
Three balls, two strikes.
Guoo!
Oh no!
He's hitting it really well.
He hits it so hard.
He's hitting it so hard.
Oh, sit.
Bunt,
Is there a bunt?
Whoa!
Wow!
Oh, wow!
You run.
I'm scared.
The flow is amazing, isn't it?
It's scary to see the way they catch the demons.
The way he plays the devil's advocate is scary, too
Okamoto, right?
Chain
It's scary, isn't it?
But it's Asano.
It'll be great if he scores here.
It's great when he decides here.
This is already Asano Player.
I'll do it to Asano Player.
From Asano's point of view.
I'll do it for him.
I'll do it.
Wow!
oh?
Wow out
I thought it was going to be a front out
I thought it was going to be the out before
It was an out.
I was scared, but...
I was pretty much on third.
It was possible.
It was like a live performance.
I knew it.
Sixth floor, front.
Let's start there.
Sixth floor.
Live.
Strike out.
Mr. Merry.
Excellent.
Number two.
Second.
Scary.
Maki is number 2.
Maki is at 2nd!
Maki is 2nd
Maki on 2.
What? I thought you got in.
No, he didn't.
Aubrun!
He hit an Aubrun.
It's Aubrun, Maki.
Aubrun, Maki.
Oh!
SUZUKI TABLE
SUZUKI table and
Suzuki table and
Eggev.
Eggive
Hazard
mmm
Hmmm...
Next.
Behind the shell.
No, let's have Okamoto give one to this one.
Jackson pitcher
He's been pitching well, hasn't he?
It's 3.1.
Seriously.
But he hasn't hit 100 pitches yet.
Well, neither of us have.
Not yet.
Hang in there. If we get out of here...
I got one.
One coming out.
Yes!
My hit, genius.
Good.
A hit.
To first base.
My hit, genius!
Next, Riser and Oshiro, Griffins
Griffin replacing the pitcher.
Oshiro is the player.
Good luck with that.
I'm afraid of bases loaded.
Woohoo!
I've got it under control!
That was close, that was close
Look out!
Tastemaster!
The Tastemaster is here.
Wow.
It's a riser.
This is a riser.
Raiser.
It's a riser.
It is a riser.
It's Reiser.
Yes!
Yay! Yay!
I hit a riser.
Lefty my hit.
Scary, scary, scary.
Goal.
Hard ball.
The bases are loaded.
Oh no, bases are loaded with two outs.
And Miyazaki!
Wow, this is scary!
I'll take care of it.
Oh, I should have worn my uniform!
Yah!
Here it is
Oh, hey.
All right.
Miyazaki
Hunt!
Nice home field.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Oh, I'm scared.
Wow.
Yeah!
Three balls.
If it's the next ball...
If it's the next ball, I'll push it out and reverse the situation.
Wow.
Yay!
All right!
Go, Motto!
Oh, here they come!
Go, Mochiron!
Smile!
Salut!
Here comes the bottom of the 8th inning.
Here it comes, bottom of the 8th inning.
Nope.
It's an attack from the captain.
Sixth.
Sixth man.
5th person
6th person
The 6th person
5th person
6th person
The 6th person
Sixth person
The first one that comes to mind is before the session.
Understood.
This time, we're going to close the oni no koto song and then we're going to play each other's
Tertiary songs?
The first song to appear in the third period
Tertiary song?
I already have one.
I've got a lot of food for you.
Please let it be “Paping”!
Paping.
Isn't it great?
Skirt Yamaguchi
Goal!
Goal! Goal!
Goal
Indeed!
The fastest tempo.
Isn't it relaxing?
I'm a demon.
I like demons.
Three ball.
We were talking about this.
It was a three-ball game.
I got a ground out on a swab ball.
Giants!
Asano.
BASTARD
I'm glad
Good
Good, good, good.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good
Have a good day.
Go, go, go!
If it hits the bat, it scores a run
Start
Start, start, start
Goal
Start
If you hit the map, you get a point!
Wow!
Yay!
Yeah!
Now, Giants.
Beautiful men!
One layer of light
Hooray!
Hooray! Hooray!
We've got him!
It's overtime.
Here comes number 4, Austin.
If it's just one shot, it's the end.
Okay, sta-mirror shot.
Triple play.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Japan pay serve
Increasing amount of burden
Finally, the real, real last one!
The 12th inning has begun.
With the runners.
Go for it!
They're cheering so loud!
Oh, man.
But...
It's raining too hard.
Two outs.
Two out.
Ovation player at third base.
player called for...
It's really something.
Something about September 7th
Too much of a meeting.
Same 12 innings.
The 12th inning was extended... and the voice player...
Honmura fell.
Last time...
Strike two.
Two outs, two strikes.
Bottom of the 12th inning.
Runner at third.
Third base.
Please subscribe to our channel!
After that
Laying down and enjoying.
Drawing.
pública
filter
mines
Raren Ara millones
It was a draw!
That was great!
It was a great match!
It was an established match for about 4.5 hours.
The first part of the game was pretty much an outburst.
But later on, we had a lot of hits.
We had a lot of chances.
There were a lot of chances!
It was really fun.
But this
While watching the game at Tokyo Dome
I was thinking that in 3 months
I was thinking that we will be standing in the dome
I was thinking that we will be standing in the Dome in 3 months.
Yes.
I feel like I have to do my best.
From now on...
I'll do my best.
Let's work hard together.
I'll do my best, too.
Thank you very much.
Please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!